(Sheldon:)If we did continue
living together,
(Sheldon:)would it be here?
(Leonard:)I don't know.
It-It could be.
(Sheldon:)Of course there's...
(Sheldon:)there's always
your apartment.
S-Sure, sure, we-we could
live in my apartment.
(Sheldon:)I hate your apartment.
(Amy:)Sorry, you brought it up?
(Sheldon:)Well, I suppose we could
find a whole new place.
(Sheldon:)You know, and, technically,
(Sheldon:)we don't even have to stay
in Pasadena.
(Sheldon:)We could, we could move
to Altadena...
(Sheldon:)or a place that doesn't
even end in "Dena."
(Amy:)It's kind of exciting.
(Amy:)I mean... we could do
whatever we want.
(Sheldon:)But what if we move
(Sheldon:)and we don't like it?
(Sheldon:)What if there's a smoker
in the building?
(Sheldon:)Or pets?
Or there could be mold.
(Sheldon:)There could be traffic noise.
(Sheldon:)I'm gonna have to learn
a whole new bus route.